[{"id":792,"question":"What is Hypervisor?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A hypervisor is a software that makes virtualization possible. It is also called Virtual Machine Monitor.","answer_b":"A hypervisor is a hardware that makes optimization possible. It is also called Virtual Machine Monitor.","answer_c":"A hypervisor is a software that makes optimization possible. It is also called Virtual Machine Monitor.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":983,"question":"How does a WHILE loop start?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"while (i <= 10)","answer_b":"while i = 1 to 10","answer_c":"while (i <= 10; i++)","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":419,"question":"Which command will delete a table called 'test':","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"DROP TABLE test","answer_b":"DROP test","answer_c":"DROP test WHERE Confirm = \"YES\"","answer_d":"DELETE test WHERE Confirm = \"YES\"","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":651,"question":"What is the option to create hard link for a directory?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"-s","answer_b":"-l","answer_c":"-f","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":593,"question":"How can we get the error when there is a problem with uploading a file?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$FILES['userfile']['error']","answer_b":"$_FILES['userfile = error']","answer_c":"$_FILES['userfile']['error']","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":606,"question":"How is a constant defined in a PHP script?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"define (\"ACONSTANT\" 123)","answer_b":"define (\"ACONSTANT\", 123);","answer_c":"define (CONSTANT, 123);","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":901,"question":"Kubernetes is written in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"C++","answer_b":"Go","answer_c":"Python","answer_d":"Java spring framework","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":243,"question":"Why is wordpress.com considered more secure than wordpress.org?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"because they limit the themes and also does not allow installing plugins.","answer_b":"because it is SSL encrypted","answer_c":"because they limit the site proxy settings","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":850,"question":"How to remove the docker image with the docker image id mentioned in the command","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker rmi fce289e99eb9","answer_b":"$ docker rmi -rf fce289e99eb9","answer_c":"$ docker rmi rf fce289e99eb9","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":845,"question":"How to list all the docker images pulled on the system with image details such as TAG\/IMAGE ID\/SIZE etc.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker img","answer_b":"$ docker --images","answer_c":"$ docker images","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1066,"question":"Which artisan command would you use to create a new Laravel Migration?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"php artisan make:migrations create_users_table","answer_b":"php artisan create:migrations create_users_table","answer_c":"php artisan make:migration create_users_table","answer_d":"php artisan make:migrations create_users_table","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":829,"question":"Each virtual machine includes the application, the necessary binaries and libraries, and an entire guest operating system - All of which may be tens of GBs in size.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":842,"question":"Following Docker command: docker commit -m \"My first update\" container_ID user_name\/repository_name  is used to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Activate default VM machine","answer_b":"Commit changes done in a Docker image","answer_c":"Build an image","answer_d":"Access a running container","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1058,"question":"What is Laravel?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Laravel is an open-source widely used PHP framework.","answer_b":"Laravel is an open-source widely used JavaScript framework.","answer_c":"Laravel is an open-source widely used Python framework.","answer_d":"Laravel is an open-source widely used Ruby framework.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Laravel"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":471,"question":"Apart from the <b> tag, what other Tag makes text bold ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<emp>","answer_b":"<strong>","answer_c":"<fat>","answer_d":"<black>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":689,"question":"Which command can be used to know the terminal type?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"tty","answer_b":"pts","answer_c":"who","answer_d":"terminal","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":453,"question":"A simple text file which tells the browser what to cache Is known as a\/an ________.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Input Files","answer_b":"HTML File","answer_c":"A Manifest File","answer_d":"Output Files","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":629,"question":"Which functions can be used to get the image's properties (size, width, and height)?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The functions are  getimagesize() for size, imagesx() for width and imagesy() for height.","answer_b":"The functions are getimagesizeof() for size, imagesxn() for width and imagesyn() for height.","answer_c":"The functions are  getsizeimage() for size, imagesx() for width and imagesy() for height.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":801,"question":"If you wish to use a base image and make modifications or personalize it, how do you do that?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker <image_name>","answer_b":"docker --pull <image_name>","answer_c":"docker pull <image_name>","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":295,"question":"How many templates can one theme contain?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Unlimited","answer_b":"1","answer_c":"Max 10","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"}]